[theme music playing]
[Dante] This is going to be our new home!
[Camia] No one will think
of doing us harm here.
[Julio] As long as this statue
stands firm in our town,
you will continue to have
honest service and leadership.
Viva Ardiente!
[all] Viva Ardiente!
[young Diego] No one in
the Ardiente family is weak.
Hey, don't jump!
[screaming]
[young Diego] Teacher Camia is helping me.
She's my new friend Lily's mom.
-Raul, stay away!
-Is it so wrong
-to be friends with you?
-Stay away!
[Camia] Go away! Get your hands off me!
Please, stop!
Your position doesn't scare me,
even if you think you own this town!
[Camia] You killed my husband! Get out!
[Emilia] You know what to do with her.
Lily… Run!
[gunshot]
[theme music continues]
I want justice for my mom and dad!
I've legally adopted you.
You'll be called Ivy Aguas.
[Ivy] This was the only way
for me to be reborn.
To become a new me.
[Prianka] Do what you must do.
Make them pay.
WELCOME TO POBLACION ARDIENTE
[Ivy] I want you to remember my face.
I am Ivy Aguas, and I am vengeance.
[Julio] These things started
the moment she came here.
[Loring] How could you
let this happen to your son?!
[Ivy] Mom? Mom? It's me.
Mom, it's me, Lily.
[Diego] Are Ivy Aguas
and Lily Cruz the same person?
Yes, Diego. I'm your old friend.
[Camia] If you're going
to fight the Ardientes,
then I'll fight with you.
[Julio] Arnaldo, you are the man!
If not for you,
your parents would've been imprisoned now,
and all of us Ardientes
would have lost our reputation.
[Diego] As long as the
Ardientes are in power,
they can't be brought down.
Someone should fight them head-on.
I'll run for governor.
Ivy!
-[Arnaldo screaming]
-[Carlotta gasping]
[screaming, sobbing]
[Rufo] Tell the congressman
that the Jaguar is here.
And he will rule Poblacion Ardiente.
[Ivy] What do you have to do
with Nanny Carlotta's death?
[gunshots]
[Ivy] Everything will be over soon.
This town will finally be free
from the Ardiente family's grip.
Stop the wedding!
[Arnaldo] I can easily kill you,
like what I did to Carlotta.
I didn't mean to.
Monster!
-I didn't mean it!
-You bastard!
-[Diego] Ivy!
-[Raul] Let go of my son!
-[guests screaming]
-[gunshot]
Lily!
-[screaming]
-[gunshots]
[Diego] Ivy, I'm right here.
We did it.
Ivy?
Ivy!
[suspenseful music playing]
-[clamoring]
-[Arnaldo] Hey! Hey!
-[man 1] Chief! Chief!
-[man 2] Arrest him!
[clamoring]
[man 3] You monster!
[man 4] Serves you right.
Arrest him! Arrest him!
[Arnaldo] No!
-[Marlon] Rot in jail!
-[Arnaldo] No!
-[Marlon] You'll rot in there!
-[man 5] Murderer!
[Fernan] You deserve to die!
-[Marlon] Murderer!
-[Fernan] Serves you right!
Don't touch me! I'm still the mayor here.
-Move! Move! Move!
-[Julio] Move!
-Grandpa! Grandpa!
-[Julio] Get out of my way!
[Arnaldo] You're going to regret this!
-[Raul] Move! Move!
-[man 6] Murderer!
-Grandpa, what's this?!
-[Emilia] Arnaldo!
[clamoring]
[Fernan] You're a family of criminals!
-Criminals, are we?
-[Arnaldo] Let me go!
You think you're actually right?
Aren't you aware that what
you did is against the law?!
You can't arrest the mayor and hurt him!
You don't have the authority to do that!
Do you have a warrant
of arrest to seize him
and bring him here?!
Whoever your ringleader is
has really led you all on!
All of you can be
arrested and sent to jail!
You have no right to be self-righteous!
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
-[Camia sobbing] Lily!
-[Diego] Auntie.
Diego, what happened to my daughter?
Is she badly hurt? Answer me! [sobbing]
She was hit in the shoulder,
but don't worry.
The doctors are doing their best.
Where is the bastard
who did this to my daughter?
Bring me Arnaldo!
I want to see him this instant!
Aunt Camia, calm down.
We'll make him pay…
for everything he did.
So please calm down.
Lily's going to be okay.
[Camia sobbing]
-[Fernan] Murderer!
-[Arnaldo] I'm not a murderer!
Quiet down!
[clamoring]
You're monsters!
That's enough!
[Julio] What do you really want?!
You want Arnaldo to go to jail?!
[in unison] Yes! He should be in jail!
-That's not going to happen!
-[Marlon] Jail him!
[Arnaldo] That's not going to happen!
-Chief!
-[man 7] Murderer!
-Put Arnaldo behind bars.
-[crowd] Yeah!
-[crowd cheering, applauding]
-[scoffs]
Grandpa! No! No! No! No! No! No!
-Take him now!
-[Marlon] That's right!
-Dad! Dad! Mom! Mom!
-[Emilia] Arnaldo!
[Arnaldo] Dad!
[crowd whooping, applauding]
Pa, what is this?
Emilia, I know what I'm doing.
[man 8] For the new Ardiente!
Do you see how furious
those people are, Chief?
[Julio] The reason why I
agreed to put Arnaldo in jail
is because you might not
be able to control them.
They'll barge in and hurt my grandson,
-or worse, kill him.
-[crowd] Diego! Diego! Diego!
-Now that Arnaldo's behind bars,
-and he's under your custody,
-[crowd] Diego! Diego! Diego!
-I'll hold you responsible…
[crowd] Diego! Diego! Diego!
-if anything bad happens to him!
-[crowd] Diego! Diego! Diego!
-[Julio] Is that clear?!
-Yes, Congressman.
-[crowd] Diego! Diego! Diego!
-[Emilia] Papa.
-Look at them!
-For the new Ardiente!
-Look at those imbeciles.
-Diego! Diego! Diego!
Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
Let them enjoy this moment.
But in the end, we'll have the last laugh.
Mark my words. I'll make
them cry tears of blood!
[crowd] Diego! Diego! Diego!
My grandson won't rot in prison…
-and all of them will realize…
-[crowd] Diego! Diego! Diego!
-what a huge mistake it was…
to go against the Ardientes!
-[man 9] For change!
-Enjoy it while it lasts, fools!
Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
-[crowd] Diego!
-[man] For real change!
[Camia] Please keep my daughter safe.
[sobbing]
Auntie, I have to go.
Nanny Loring, Uncle Pandoy.
Take care of everything here.
Diego. Where are you going?
What they've done to my
grandson is illegal confinement.
Arnaldo was not caught committing a crime
or in the act of committing one.
He was not given due process.
Even his arrest was illegal
because there was no warrant served.
And the video of his alleged confession
is clearly tampered with.
So I don't see any reason
for my grandson not to be
released from jail immediately.
You're right, Congressman.
We can file a petition for habeas corpus
to dismiss the case.
[Julio] Good.
But, Julio…
A lot of people heard Arnaldo's confession
in front of Ivy at the wedding.
[laughs gently]
[Emilia] And, Papa, if that gets out
during the preliminary investigation…
the case will be heard in court.
It's simple, really. I have a solution.
Cut off the tongue of
anyone who tries to talk.
Slice off the ears of those
who will listen to them.
Have they forgotten
who they're up against?
We are the Ardientes.
We can break, bend,
or turn the law around…
to how we want it to.
We can also erase or alter any
evidence that they might have.
Jepoy, what are you doing? Stop it.
-What's happening to you?
-This is all my fault, Anna!
Arnaldo managed to snatch my gun.
Of all people, he got mine!
[breathes heavily]
If I hadn't interfered with the plan,
this wouldn't have happened.
[Jepoy breathing heavily]
This is my fault, Anna.
Jepoy.
[breathing heavily]
[exhales]
Ivy is Lily Cruz.
She's my daughter.
She had to hide her identity to
exact revenge on the Ardientes.
Promise me that no one
will find out about it.
The Ardientes will kill Lily
if they find out the truth about her.
Yes, Camia. We promise.
We will take this secret to our graves.
We're the only ones who can help
each other fight the Ardientes.
Thank you.
[dramatic music playing]
[reporter] A citizen's arrest
was conducted by the people
of Poblacion Ardiente
against Mayor Arnaldo Torillo.
This was after he confessed to killing
Carlotta Navarro and Nimfa Naig.
[Emilia's hitman]
You won't get anything from me!
[man 1] Murderer!
[Diego] Put these men in jail
and arrest Emilia Torillo!
What is this all about?!
She attempted to have Ivy Aguas
killed to stop the wedding.
Who, me?!
And they were also the ones
who planted the bomb.
You tried to stop the wedding?
[Emilia] That's a lie!
I have the evidence.
This contains records of phone
calls and text messages
between Emilia Torillo and her hitman.
Honestly, Diego!
Papa, why would you believe this bastard?
And how will you prove that the
number used is mine, pray tell?
Who ordered you?
Tell us who gave you orders!
-Admit it!
-Speak up.
-The devil!
-[chuckles sarcastically]
[Emilia's hitman] It was the
devil who ordered me to do it!
-Liar! Liar!
-[man 2] Blaming it on the devil, eh?
-Arrest him!
-[laughing]
-[police officer] Leave him to us!
-[man 2] Arrest him!
-[laughing]
-[Diego] Arrest him!
-[man 2] Give them the gun!
-[man 3] Here!
Nice try, Diego.
But, next time,
if you're looking for someone
to help you take us down,
don't search here.
Go find help in the dumpster,
where you belong!
-They're liars.
-All of them.
Your family is the worst
piece of garbage there is!
And I'll make sure that
you'll pay for all your crimes.
Oh, really, Diego?
Then we're also going
to make sure that you go down.
You think I don't know that you
and Ivy planned to overthrow us?
Oh, stop it, Emilia!
Let's end this pointless little act!
[Julio] You.
And all of you!
If any of you wish
to file cases against me
or any member of my family, go ahead!
It's your right. But let me warn you.
We will be ready to face
all your charges and allegations
at the proper time
and in the proper forum.
Now, I do not need
any more of this aggravation!
Emilia. Raul. Let's go.
Let's put an end to this
third-rate circus act!
-[Fernan] Murderers!
-[man] Murderers!
Records say she's okay.
I think she can go out in a few days.
Okay.
-Hello.
-Hi, doc.
Ivy's condition is stable.
She's lucky the bullet
didn't hit her heart.
-Thank you, doc.
-[doctor] All right.
-Thank you.
-Excuse me. Excuse me.
[Loring] Thank you.
[soft music playing]
Lily, dear…
I'm right here, okay?
I won't leave your side.
Let me out of here! Hey! Hey!
I'm the mayor of this place!
Why are you keeping me in here?! [screams]
[thuds]
Let me out of here!
Hey! Shut it! You're so noisy!
-[thuds]
-What did you say?! Huh?!
You may be the boss in here,
but I'm the mayor.
Come here. Let me rub that back for you!
[laughs]
[scoffs] No! No!
[screaming]
[Arnaldo] No, no, no, no. No. No.
[groaning]
[tense music playing]
You did all this! You!
You ruined us! How could I let you?!
You're pathetic!
You and Ivy were ruined a long time ago.
Since the day you killed Nanny Carlotta.
[tense music intensifies]
You'll rot in here.
And no matter what…
you will never get Ivy back.
[Arnaldo laughs]
You will rot in here.
[groans] Where's Ivy?
Tell me where she is.
I just want to know where she is.
Come on, tell me.
From one man to another,
it's lonely in here.
Come on, just tell her
we have a honeymoon to do.
I'm the mayor. I'm loaded with money.
I can convert this cell into
a hotel room for all I care.
Just tell her, come on. Come on.
Please. I miss Ivy.
I miss everything about her.
I miss her body. I miss her.
I miss her lips. Please tell her, come on.
I miss her lips.
I miss everything about her.
Do you hear me? She's mine! Hey! Hey!
She's mine! Diego!
[tense music intensifies]
Grandpa! Mom!
[sobs]
[groans]
[door opens]
-Oh. Diego.
-Uncle.
[quietly] Where did you go?
Nanny.
Where have you been?
How's Ivy?
[soft music playing]
Auntie.
Diego.
How are you, Auntie? How's Ivy?
She still hasn't woken up.
I'm sorry about all this, Auntie.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect Ivy.
No, Diego.
Thank you…
because you were
planning Arnaldo's downfall.
Diego, thank you for not
abandoning my daughter.
[soft music playing]
Auntie Camia, Ivy's tough.
I'm sure she'll get through this.
I know it.
And she won't let the Ardientes win.
[instrumental theme music playing]
Lily.
[whispering] Ivy's awake.
Lily?
[instrumental theme music playing]
Don't worry. We know now.
[music fades]
[reporter] While Mayor Arnaldo Torillo
is now detained
here at the provincial jail,
the Ardiente
family says they are confident
the truth will come out
and he will soon be freed.
[reporter] Señor Julio,
do you have a message for
the people of Ardiente?
To the people of Ardiente,
your Señor Julio is calling upon you
to not believe hearsay from
our political rivals trying to ruin us.
My grandson did nothing wrong.
He is an innocent man.
[reporter] Is it true you threatened
the people who arrested the mayor?
[Julio] Let me tell you this,
everyone can understand
even the basics of the law.
You know that Arnaldo's arrest is illegal.
It is against the law!
But what did I do? I allowed it to happen.
Even when I knew it was wrong,
I allowed it to happen.
Why? So that we can avoid even more chaos
that would have hurt
the people of Ardiente.
That's what's important to us--
everyone's safety.
Citizens of Ardiente, you are my children.
And I will always love you and put you
ahead of everything else.
That's why I sacrificed my own grandson.
I let his arrest happen
so we could avoid more violence,
more chaos,
and more possibilities for the people
of Ardiente to get hurt.
Now, if you will excuse us,
it has been a very taxing
and trying day for our family.
I'm sure the Ardientes will
send people here to spy on us.
[exhales]
[tense music playing]
Thank you all for your concern,
but the Ardientes can't see
or know about us being together.
Mr. Pandoy, Miss Loring…
I'm sorry, but you need
to leave right away.
Jepoy, Anna…
go with them.
[tense music playing]
You too, Mom.
You need to leave.
Attorney, I'll say it again.
I want Arnaldo out of
that stinking rathole
as soon as possible.
-Yes, Congressman.
-And please. Please!
Make sure the media doesn't get anything
that might tarnish our name,
especially not Arnaldo's.
Yes, Papa.
Now, please tell me…
Who was behind all that bedlam?
Papa, isn't it obvious?
It was Ivy and Diego
who staged everything
to bring Arnaldo down.
Hold on, Emilia. Are you sure about that?
Do you have proof to back up your claims?
[sighs] Come on, Raul.
Stop protecting and defending
your bastard son, already.
It's so obvious!
Papa, Diego came in right before
Arnaldo's little confession.
That was too timely!
Plus, we should award Ivy
for the worst acting ever!
[sighs] It's like she didn't even try!
And, Papa,
they staged everything
in the grandest wedding.
It's obvious they plotted it
so everyone will see Arnaldo's downfall.
I must say, you have a point, Emilia.
But with our current situation…
we can't be reckless.
We cannot be carried away by our emotions.
We have to be sure because
the public's eyes are on us.
It's as if we're the bad guys.
So, if we are to hit back at anyone,
I want to make sure
we hit the right target.
I need proof.
[Julio sighs]
Julio… you should see this.
[tense music playing]
That's Arthur Vergara.
One of Camia Cruz's witnesses.
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
[somber music playing]
Mom, you have to leave too.
Whether you like it or not,
I'm not leaving.
Lily, you were shot!
Arnaldo almost killed you!
Emilia tried to murder you!
What more reason do you need?
That wasn't the first attempt on my life,
and it certainly won't be the last.
What I'm doing is dangerous, Mom.
You know that, right?
When will all this be over?
When I bury your corpse?
The next time something
like this happens, remember…
I'll be the one
to take the bullet for you.
[tense music playing]
[door closes]
Hold on. Didn't he die? Bottled in a drum?
Apparently not.
He was the one who leaked
Arnaldo's confession on live TV.
[laughing]
[laughing continues]
You mean to tell me
that all it took to tarnish our name
was one crazy bastard?!
[Julio continues laughing]
How could we let this happen?!
Well?! How?!
How was a crazy person able
to make us all look stupid?!
You. Come over here.
You have been the head of my
army for the past 16 years.
How many times have you messed up?
Well? [scoffs]
Too many times to count.
That's why you can't answer me.
Congressman, I did my job well.
Do you remember Governor Alvarez
and that reporter you wanted dead?
-I did a clean job.
-[Julio scoffs]
Two examples from almost a lifetime ago!
And if my memory serves me right,
my rule is that
you are only as good as your last job.
And if we look at it…
your last job was a mess
because you weren't able
to stop the public
from barging into Arnaldo's wedding!
What was wrong?! Tell me.
I gave you the weaponry!
I gave you the manpower!
I even gave you a chopper!
But what did you do?! What did you do?
Nothing! Zilch! Zero! Nada!
You were just running
around like a headless chicken!
You couldn't even hold back a crowd!
I am going to give you one last chance.
Bring me the head of Arthur Vergara!
Or else, I'll have
your head roll in the plaza!
Understood, Congressman.
You better be sure!
Now, these people think they can
just push our family around.
They're disrespecting us!
Well, I want everyone to know…
no one in this world can bring me down.
Not in a million years!
And I want you to spread the news…
that Julio Ardiente is
coming down on them,
and I am coming down
on them with a vengeance!
I am going to make it rain fire
and brimstone on them.
[Julio] They'll regret the day
that they were born.
-Mom, let's go!
-Hurry up!
There! That's where I last saw Arthur!
Sir! Where's my payment?
What are you talking about?
Scram! Search the house!
[suspenseful music playing]
Sir, negative.
He escaped. Let's go.
Sir, he's not here. He was able to escape.
[Arthur] Ma'am Ivy.
Here's the 20 million pesos
of ransom money
that Mayor Arnaldo paid me
for your release.
No one should make use of it
other than you.
Thank you for the protection
you've given me.
Ma'am? Miss Aguas?
Excuse me, ma'am.
Here are the documents
needed for our head office.
Ma'am, I'm very sorry about
what happened to your wedding.
Irene, that's not part of your job.
So, let's not talk about it anymore.
Yes, ma'am.
Open the bag.
Wow, Miss Aguas, that's a lot of money.
I want you to deposit
it all into the accounts
of Shining Light Foundation,
New Home Orphanage,
the Children's Hospital,
and Homes for the Aged.
-Under whose name, ma'am?
-Anonymous.
That's so kind of you, ma'am.
Irene, that money isn't from me.
It was stolen by the Ardientes,
so I'm returning it to the
people who deserve it.
You may go now.
Tell the guards to escort you.
Okay, ma'am.
[Irene] Excuse me.
[Emilia on TV] Arnaldo, my son…
Are you okay?
I'll be praying for you tonight.
[Emilia] I'll visit you again
tomorrow, okay?
[Emilia] As for your question earlier,
yes, I will continue the rehabilitation
and education programs for our inmates.
So, you're still committed
to public service
despite what happened?
Of course I am. I'm a mother.
It's in my nature to care for others,
especially after seeing how terrible
their living conditions truly are.
And as you can see,
Mayor Arnaldo Ardiente
has no VIP treatment.
Open it.
Mayor, wake up.
Come with me.
[Emilia] Please rest assured that
we will not abuse our position
to gain privilege.
[door opens]
My son will be eating, bathing,
and sharing a restroom
with all the other inmates here.
Isn't that right, guys?
-Viva Ardiente!
Mayor. We need to return you
to the cell. You have a visitor.
Ivy! Ivy, how are you?
-Don't touch me.
-No. I'm so glad you're back!
How's your wound? How are you?
-I said don't touch me!
-Okay, okay, okay!
I just want to make sure you're okay.
I'm doing fine.
Well, thank you for being here.
Thank you for visiting me.
Thank you. I missed you.
I missed you so much!
-You did?
-Yes.
[tense music playing]
I didn't come here to get
back together with you.
I came here to make sure
you'll go insane in this prison!
I already regret what I did to Carlotta.
What more do you want?
This isn't enough!
I want your conscience to eat at you.
Will you ever forgive me?
You don't know how it feels
to lose a mother.
Would you like to experience it?
I can help you.
So you'll know the answer
to your question.
By the way, send my regards to Emilia.
Given the fact that she wanted me killed,
tell her it's only a matter of time
before she gets what she's looking for.
Uh…
What did Mom do to you?
You'll go insane here, Arnaldo.
What did Mom do to you? Wait! Ivy, please!
What did Mom do to you?
[stutters] Tell me. Tell me.
No, no. Ivy. Ivy! Ivy!
Hey, call her for me! Ivy!
Ivy, come back!
Ivy! Ivy! Ivy! Ivy! Ivy!
[tense music playing]
Ivy, come back here! Ivy! Ivy!
How's my grandson?
Ivy! Ivy! Ivy!
-It's Arnaldo, Papa!
-[Arnaldo] Get off me!
[screaming] Ivy! Ivy! Ivy!
-[Emilia] Arnaldo?
-[Arnaldo screaming] Ivy!
Ivy! Ivy! Ivy! Ivy!
-[Emilia] Arnaldo?!
-[Arnaldo] Ivy!
-[Emilia] Arnaldo!
-[Arnaldo] Let me go!
Arnaldo! Let him go!
Let go of my son! Stop, stop!
Let go of me. I'm all right.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
-That's enough! Stop it!
-[sobbing] I'm okay. I'm okay.
Mom, get me out of here.
-I'm here. I'm here.
-Get me out of here, Mom!
Please! Please let me out of here.
I wanna make your life a living hell
because this is all your fault!
It's all your fault!
-[Julio] Arnaldo!
-It's all your fault!
-[Emilia grunts]
-It's your fault too!
-[Julio] Arnaldo!
-I will kill you!
I will kill you! I will kill you!
-[Emilia] Papa!
-Ivy!
-[Raul] Arnaldo, that's enough!
-[Julio] Arnaldo!
[sobbing, screaming] Ivy! Ivy! Ivy! Ivy!
-[stun gun sparks]
-[tense music playing]
[police officer] I'm sorry, ma'am.
[Emilia gasps] Papa!
I understand. I know you had to do it.
[Raul] Sir, help us.
[Emilia] Papa!
-Carry him to his cell.
-[Raul] Let's go.
Are you okay?
-[Emilia breathes heavily]
-[gate squeaks]
[tense music playing]
Papa, is he going to be okay?
[Julio stutters] Yeah, I think he is.
Is he really going to stay here?
Such a miserable place!
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Mom?
Lily.
Mom, I'm sorry it took me a while to call.
It's okay, dear.
What's important is I got
to hear your voice.
That's enough for me.
How are you, dear?
I really miss you.
When will I see you again?
I miss you too, Mom.
And don't worry.
We'll see each other soon.
Very soon.
Okay, then. Always take care of yourself.
[dramatic music playing]
[music fades]
See, Papa?
See? It's right there.
That CCTV footage won't lie.
Ivy Aguas visited Arnaldo
before we came in.
I wouldn't be surprised if that woman
slandered me to my son.
That's why Arnaldo's so mad at me.
And he almost killed me!
Well… You did try to
kill his fiancée, didn't you?
So, technically, your son's right
when he said this is your fault.
-What?!
-[scoffs] Come on, Emilia.
From the very beginning,
you've tried to undermine
Ivy and Arnaldo's relationship.
And even though you knew
I wanted their wedding to continue,
you still disobeyed me.
You actually tried to have Ivy killed.
Excuse me, Papa. That's incorrect.
I never admitted to being
behind the assassination
plot against Ivy,
so technically speaking,
I had nothing to do with that.
[sarcastic chuckle]
You can lie to the public,
you can lie through your teeth…
but you can't lie to me.
I have eyes and ears all over my city.
That's why I know the truth.
Now…
Do you have anything you want to say
before I tell you your punishment?
Yes, Papa.
This is not about hatred
or jealousy towards Ivy Aguas.
I can smell the traitor
in that woman, Papa.
She plotted everything
to bring Arnaldo down.
I know that. I can feel it.
Hunting down Arthur Vergara
is just a waste of time.
We should get the head of the snake,
and that's Ivy Aguas, Papa.
We should kill her!
We should kill her as early as now, Papa.
Before the media finds her
and asks for an interview
that can destroy our family's image!
And if we do that, Papa?
You know that we can blame it
on our enemies, right?
And with that, we might even get
the sympathy of the people.
Papa…
Ivy Aguas is better off dead,
and you know it.
[exhales sharply]
[tense music playing]
Do it.
[tense music intensifies]
Well? How did your meeting with Papa go?
You know, I can't believe
that you left me in there again!
Why? What would I tell him
if I was there? [scoffs]
Besides, Emilia, you did plan
to have Ivy killed, right?
You should be grateful
that I kept my mouth shut.
Well, that's what you are good at.
-Keeping your mouth shut.
-[Raul scoffs]
At least some people
have the guts to defend me…
unlike you.
Wait. Who are you referring to?
Jaguar? You think he's all that?
You want the truth? Yes, it's Jaguar!
You know, Raul, I wish you were Jaguar.
Maybe then you'd be able to say
and do something!
Our family is falling apart.
Our son is in jail,
but you're not doing anything.
All you do is just nothing! Nothing!
Hold on, Emilia.
Don't ever underestimate
the things I do for our family!
What have you done for our family, Raul?
Humor me. And if you keep pulling me down,
I have no other choice but to dump you!
I'm not done talking yet!
Are you threatening me?
Do whatever you want, then!
I dare you, Emilia!
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
People, I would like you
to meet the new head
of our private army,
Colonel Jose Ruel Sanggano.
Hello, ma'am. Hello, sir.
And I would like everybody else to know
that we will be making
a lot of personnel changes.
So, for the rest of our staff…
Please sit down.
They better think twice,
if they do not perform
according to my standards.
For your information,
Col. Sanggano used to lead
the military operations
in the whole of Mindanao.
That's why I am very confident in him.
So, where's your former head, Papa?
Emilia, you know how I treat
my men who are incompetent.
I sent him on a vacation…
to the cemetery. [laughs]
That is why my men have life insurance.
Because I care for my people.
I'm sure everyone is lining up
to work for you, Papa.
It has always been the case.
Thank you for joining us again, Colonel.
Thank you, sir.
[phone ringing]
Boss?
[Jaguar] Jepoy.
Report to me immediately.
We have something to discuss.
All right, boss.
Jepoy, where are you going?
You and Miss Camia go ahead. I'll follow.
-Where are you off to now?
-Anna, it's nothing.
[unsettling music playing]
Anna, is Jepoy hiding something from us?
No.
[ominous music playing]
[beeps]
Some of my men saw you at Mayor
Arnaldo and Ivy Aguas' wedding.
What were you doing there?
Simple, boss.
I was going to kill Arnaldo,
but I didn't get the chance.
I want to make him feel the
torture they made me go through.
-Leave Mayor Arnaldo to me.
-Why, boss?
Are we supposed to protect him?
Do you know what happens
to those who question God?
They get struck by lightning.
And, in this place, I am God.
I am your God.
-Boss.
-And this is my lightning bolt.
You don't want to be struck
by lightning, do you?
[suspenseful music playing]
Understood, boss.
[music intensifies]
[police officer] This way, sir.
[melancholic music playing]
[door opens]
Clean him up.
[door closes]
[sighs]
What happened to you, Arnaldo?
You're the mayor of this city
and soon-to-be governor.
Arnaldo! You were the
golden boy of our family.
How could you let your life be ruined…
by a woman?!
Now, you just sit there and cry!
Stop it! Wipe your tears.
And be the man that I trained you to be!
Arnaldo, please.
Tell me what I can do to help you.
Arnaldo, I will do anything. Anything!
What do you want?! What do you need?!
Ivy.
Give me Ivy.
[melancholic music playing]
[sniffles]
[sobbing] I'm begging you. Give me Ivy.
Grandpa! I'm begging you.
[sobbing] Give me Ivy!
I need Ivy!
I can't live without her!
That's all I need.
That's all I need in my life.
She's all I need. [sobbing]
It's just really lonely here.
[breathing heavily]
I need her in this bed.
I want her. Here. With me.
Please, give her to me.
It's really sad in this room,
and I need my wife here!
If you really love me,
you will give her to me.
Are you listening?
You will give her to me.
[sobs] Give her to me.
Please!
[Arnaldo] Ivy…
[melancholic music playing]
No! No! No! [sobbing]
[Julio] I'm here
to make you an offer, Ivy.
A hundred million pesos.
In exchange for what?
Get back together with my grandson.
[Camia] What are you going to do?
Are you going to help Arnaldo recover
after you tore him down?
Arnaldo is the weakness of the Ardientes--
Emilia, Raul, and especially Julio.
So I need Arnaldo to finish off
the Ardientes once and for all.
Let the games begin!
Charges against Mayor Arnaldo Torillo
were dismissed.
[Camia] They've proven yet again
that they have the law at their disposal.
[thuds]
[theme music playing]